Inventory of the Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
Broadside Case Collection, 1896 - 2004
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-79
6
13
The Broadside Case Collection contains many oversized documents from a variety of sources. Included are photographs, architectural drawings, posters, maps, and other material related to Wesleyan University.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Acquired from multiple sources. See Special Collections & Archives staff for more information.
Collection Overview
The Broadside Case Collection contains many oversized documents from a variety of sources. Included are photographs, architectural drawings, posters, maps, and other material related to Wesleyan University.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.); Posters.; Photographs.; Architectural drawings.; Maps.
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Oversize plates, illustrations, and paper examples
  - Oversize plates from the rare book collection, illustrations, and Book Arts Press paper examples (Drawer 1)
- Posters and book jackets
  - Deborah Hay posters
    - Deborah Hay. The Man Who Grew Common in Wisdom. CFA Theater. September 20th, circa early 1980s. (Drawer 2, Folder 1)
    - Pauline Oliveros, Composer. Deborah Hay, Choreographer. Center for the Arts. September 15, 1984.
    - Deborah Hay, Choreographer. Bill Jeffers, Composer. The Movement of Light. Zilker Hillside Theater. May 20-21, 1983.
    - Deborah Hay, Choreographer. Bill Jeffers, Composer. The Movement of Light. Zilker Hillside Theater. May 20-21, 1983.
    - Deborah Hay, Pauline Oliveros, Tina Girouard. Tasting the Blaze. Austin Opera House. April 19-20, 1985.
  - Wesleyan Performing Arts Posters
    - Ollie Griffith, Woodwinds; Ray Herrmann, Drums/Percussion. Improvised Music. Second Stage. May 5-7, 1992. (Folder 2)
    - Camilla DeLeon, Director. It's a Lonesome Old Town When You're Not Around. Second Stage. Undated.
    - Mark Knowles, Director. The Vaudeville Follies. '92 Theater, Wesleyan. Undated.
    - William Braun, Piano; Julie Charland Ribchinski, Cello; Peter Standaart, Flute. An Evening of Chamber Music. Crowell Concert Hall, Center for the Arts, Wesleyan University. October 11, 1986. [2 posters]
    - Mark Knowles, Director. The Vaudeville Follies. '92 Theater, Wesleyan. April 22-24, year unknown.
    - Wesleyan University Concert Choir and Schola Cantorum. Ralph Vaughan Williams. South Congregational Church, Hartford, Connecticut. November 8, 1973.
    - Wesleyan University Concert Choir. Choral Music of Brahms. Wesleyan Memorial Chapel. April 26, 1973.
    - Namino Torii, Yoshikazu Iwamoto, Kinuko Shirane. Sankyoku- Classical Japanese Music. World Music Hall. November 21, 1975.
    - Wesleyan University. Graduate Program in World Music. Center for the Arts. Faculty, 1978-9.
    - An Evening of Traditional African Drumming and Dance with Flute. Crowell Concert Hall. December 12, 1975.
    - Mr. Prawotosaputro, Gamelan Leader. Javanese Gamelan and Dance. Wesleyan Arena. April 22, 1972.
    - Teresa Escandon. Piano Recital. Crowell Concert Hall, Center for the Arts. January 30, 1976.
    - Abraham Adzenyah, Freeman Donkor, S.D. Asiama. Crowell Concert Hall. May 9, 1975.
    - Gilbert and Sullivan. Mikado. Wesleyan Memorial Chapel. February 23-4, year unknown.
    - Charles Berman, Guitar; Mark Powell, Bass; Michael Holmes, Organ; Fred Holister, Drums; Oliver Griffith, Tenor; Kimberly Clark, Trumpet. A Midnight Concert of Reggae. No location, undated
    - Adam Dydak, Piano Recital. Ronald Epstein, Piano. Two Concerts. May 13, 1976.
    - Richard Coff, violin; Naaz Hosseini, violin; George Barth, piano; Rolf Norgaard, Cello; Phillippi Dunne, Guitar. An Evening of Chamber Music. Wesleyan Memorial Chapel. April 10, year unknown.
    - Various Artists. Woodwind Quintet Recital. World Music Hall. April 3, 1976.
    - Navaratri Festival. World Music Hall, Center for the Arts, Wesleyan Univ. September 24-29, 1976.
    - Isaac Hurwitz, Conductor. The Wesleyan Orchestra. Crowell Concert Hall. November 24, year unknown.
    - Jon Barlow, piano; Isaac Hurwitz, violin. Wesleyan Memorial Chapel. April 21, year unknown.
    - Peter Armstrong, Pianist. Crowell Concert Hall. April 13, year unknown.
    - The Wesleyan University Schola Cantorum presents Music of Giovanni Pierluigi da Palestrina and Johann Sebastian Bach. Memorial Chapel. March 21, 1973.
    - Various Artists. South Indian Music Concert. Romance Languages Bldg. June 1, 1973.
    - Adam Dydak, Piano Recital. Ronald Epstein, Piano. Two Concerts. May 13, 1976. (Copy).
    - Students of Sharda Sahai. Concert of North Indian Music. 300 High Street, Wesleyan. March 16, year unknown.
    - Isaac Hurwitz. Stravinsky. by The Wesleyan Chamber Orchestra. Memorial Chapel. October 28, 1972.
    - Isaac Hurwitz, Conductor. Mass in C Major. by the Wesleyan University Chamber Orchestra and Concert Choir. Memorial Chapel. March 3,4, 1973.
    - Ilene Goldstein. Piano Recital. Honors College, March 13, year unknown.
    - Namino Torii; Ryudow Takahashi. A Concert of Classical Japanese Music. World Music Hall. March 7, 1977.
    - Various Artists. A Concert of South Indian Music. Crowell Concert Hall. April 15, 1977.
    - Namino Torii; Ryudow Takahashi. A Concert of Classical Japanese Music. World Music Hall. March 7, 1977.
    - Ensemble Concert. Jazz. Crowell Concert Hall. October 11, 1976.
    - Peter Sacco, Violin; Virginia Weckstrom, Piano. A Recital. Crowell Concert Hall. April 28, 1976.
    - Namino Torii; Ryudow Takahashi. Sankyoku: A Concert of Classical Japanese Music. Crowell Concert Hall. November 19, 1976.
    - Bill Barron, Director. Wesleyan Lab Band. Crowell Concert Hall. April 16, 1976.
    - Navaratri Festival. World Music Hall, Center for the Arts, Wesleyan Univ. September 24-29, 1976.
    - Jean Redpath. Crowell Concert Hall. October 22, year unknown.
    - An Evening of Traditional African Drumming and Dance with Flute. Crowell Concert Hall. May 14, 1976.
    - Peter Armstrong, Pianist. Crowell Concert Hall. April 13, year unknown.
    - Gregory Bonenberger, guitarist. World Music Hall. April 19, year unknown.
    - Jean Redpath, Scottish Folksinger. Songs of Pleasure and Love. March 12, 1975. Crowell Concert Hall.
    - Various Artists. The Violin Trio and Palghat Mani Lyer. November 7, 1975. World Music Hall.
    - Isaac Hurwitz, Conductor. Wesleyan University Orchestra. A Program of Nineteenth Century Music. March 7, 1969. Wesleyan Memorial Chapel.
    - Isaac Hurwitz, Conductor. Wesleyan University Orchestra. March 9, Crowell Concert Hall, Wesleyan. March 14, The James Lippincott Goodwin Theatre, Trinity, year unknown.
    - Henry Brant. Meteor Farm. Crowell Concert Hall. March 3, 1984.
    - Wesleyan-Smith Glee Clubs. Responsorial Psalmody. October 18, 1970. Memorial Chapel.
    - Various Artists. Jubilee; a festival of African-American Music. April 15-17, year unknown.
    - Anton Chekhov's The Three Sisters, undated (Folder 3)
    - Tennessee Williams, 27 Wagons Full of Cotton February 5-7, year unknown. '92 Theater.
    - Bill Francisco, Director. The Typists and the Tiger, two comedies by Murray Schisgal. February 19, 20, year unknown '92 Theater.
    - Bill Francisco, Director. Waiting for Godot and Old Times. Written by Samuel Beckett. April 30, May 1-2, year unknown '92 Theater.
    - The Hot l Baltimore by Lanford Wilson, undated.
    - The Hot l Baltimore by Lanford Wilson. Dir. by Jeffrey Lane. December 4-6, year unknown. '92 Theater.
    - Jeffrey Lane, Director. The Three Sisters. April 15-17, year unknown, '92 Theater.
    - Four Films. Chameleon, Satin Doll, Kuttner Abroad, Murder After Hours. Cinema. May 9, 1977.
    - Various Films. April 5, year unknown. Center for the Arts Cinema.
    - The Wesleyan Film Program Presents, 3 Films: Beyond the Wizard of Oz, The Ruthyn Curse, Awakening. February 14, year unknown, Science Tower.
    - The Films of Nicholas Ray. Wesleyan Film Series, undated.
    - Films by Wesleyan Film-makers. May 21, 1969. 02 Shanklin.
    - John Monroe, Director. Wedding Band by Alice Childress. Center for the Arts Theater. March 4-6, year unknown.
    - Alwin Nikolais, Murray Louis Dance Company. Mercy Auditorium. May 11, 1968. (Poster and Pamphlet).
    - Genesis, a Meditation. Members of the Ensemble, undated.
    - Bill Francisco. 6 Characters in search of an Author. by Luigi Pirandello. February, 1977. CFA Theater.
    - No Place to Be Somebody a play by Charles Gordone. Dir. by John Monroe. CFA Theater. December 4-6, 1981.
    - Il Servitore? a comedy Dir. by Bill Francisco. May 1-3, 1975. CFA Theater.
    - Wesleyan University Theater Department presents...Vinnie Burrows in Walk Together Children September 14, 1974. James Cunningham and the Acme Dance Company. September 27, 28, 1974. Indians by Arthur Kopit, Dir. by Bill Francisco. October 17-19, 1974. The Balcony by Jean Genet, Dir. by Fredrik De Boer. Nov. 21-23, 1974.
    - Endgame by Samuel Beckett. Theater, Center for the Arts. January 30-February 1, 1975.
    - As You Like It by William Shakespeare. March 5-8, year unknown. Theater, Center for the Arts.
    - Genesis, a meditation. dir. by Fritz deBoer, undated.
    - The Chalk Garden by Enid Bagnold, Dir. by Fritz deBoer. Nov 19-21, year unknown. CFA theater.
  - Wesleyan Events Posters
    - The Annual Mansfield Freeman Lecture by Ye Junjian. My life as a Chinese Intellectual, and Being a Writer in the people's Republic. October 20, 21, year unknown. Colloquium Room, CFA. No year. (Folder 4)
    - The Archer on the Franks Casket: The Survival of Homeric Myth in Early Medieval England. Amy Vandersall. March 1, year unknown. 100 Davison Art Center.
    - Art Dept. Lecture: Anthony Cutler. In Search of the Non-Existent: The Archetypal Illuminated Cycle. February 19, 1975. 100 Davison Art Center.
    - The Annual Mansfield Freeman Lecture by Ronald P. Dore. Nationalism and Internationalism in Modern Japan. March 26, 1987. Honors College, Wesleyan University.
    - Kasimir Malevich: the Avant-Garde and the Russian Revolution. Alan C. Birnholz. February 15, year unknown. 100 Davison Art Center.
    - Charles Eames. Design in Society. April 21, 1977. Cinema, Center for the Arts.
    - The Archer on the Franks Casket: The Survival of Homeric Myth in Early Medieval England. Amy Vandersall. March 1, year unknown. 100 Davison Art Center. (Copy).
    - The Two-Pronged Pen of Gunter Grass. Lecture by A. Leslie Willson. November 13, 1980. Cinema, Center for the Arts. (Copy).
    - Two Talks by David Zatz. 1. Stone, Brick, Iron and the Urban Scene. April 18, year unknown, Davison Art Center. 2. Paolo Solari at Arconsanti. April 19, year unknown, Room 107 Shanklin.
    - Kafka's Clothes. Mark Anderson. Honors College, Russell House. April 16, 1987.
    - What is Dada? May 2, year unknown. COL Lounge.
  - Posters and Book Jackets Designed by William Van Saun
    - Poems by Richard Tillinghast. The Knife and Other Poems. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket (Folder 5)
    - Poems by Barbara L. Greenberg. The Spoils of August. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Commencement, Wesleyan University. June 9, 1968.
    - Campus Directory and Regulations, Wesleyan University Bulletin. 1967-68.
    - Poems by Marge Piercy. Breaking Camp. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - John Rogers The People's Sculptor: His Life Work. by David H. Wallace.
    - Poems by Richard Tillinghast. Sleep Watch. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket.
    - Poems by James Wright. Shall We Gather at the River? Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Richard Tillinghast. Sleep Watch. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket (Copy).
    - Poems by Edwin Honig. Spring Journal. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Record Cover-- Wesleyan Perspective. Andy Gaus '68, Bill Beeman '68.
    - Poems by Edwin Honig. Spring Journal. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket (Copy).
    - Poems by James Dickey. Poems, 1957-67. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Richard Howard. The Damages. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Alkahest, American College Poetry 2, Fall 1968. Wesleyan University Press
    - Poems by Josephine Miles. Kinds of Affection. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Beyond Eagle and Swastica by Kurt P. Tauber. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Donald Haberman, The Plays of Thornton Wilder; a Critical Study. Book Jacket. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Judith Hemschemeyer. I Remember the Room was Filled with Light. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Philip Levine. Not this Pig. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Lou Lipsitz. Cold Water. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Edwin Honig. Spring Journal. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Donald Justice. Night Light. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Owen Barfield. Romanticism Comes of Age. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Eleanor Lerman. Armed Love. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Ruth Miller. The Poetry of Emily Dickinson. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Gray Burr. A Choice of Attitudes. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Vassar Miller. Onions and Roses. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Judith Hemschemeyer. Very Close and Very Slow. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Anne Stevenson, Correspondences: A Family History in Letters. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Charles Wright. Bloodlines. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Lawrence Kearny. Kingdom Come. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Barbara L. Greenberg. The Spoils of August. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by James Tate. Viper Jazz. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by W.R. Moses. Passage. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Mike Lowery. Masks of the Dreamer. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Al Zolynas, The New Physics. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Al Zolynas, The New Physics. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket (more complete copy).
    - Poems by Steve Orlen, Permission to Speak. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Adam Lefevre, Everything All at Once. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Ricardo Alonso, Cimarron. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Frederick Buell, Full Summer. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Russell Edson, The Reason Why the Closet-Man is Never Sad. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Poems by Cynthia Genser, Taking on the Local Color. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - The National Tradition of Historical Thought from Herder to the Present. By Georg G. Iggers. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
    - Adolf Grunbaum. Modern Science and Zeno's Paradoxes. Wesleyan University Press. Book Jacket
  - Wesleyan Events Posters
    - Plate Five: The Hogarth Engraving. Davison Art Center Collection, Wesleyan University, undated (Folder 6)
    - Wesleyan University Campus Guide and Map 1981-1982. Sesquicentennial. Wesleyan's 150th Birthday, 1831-1981.
    - Summer at the Center. Events for July 9 to July 17, year unknown. Center for the Arts, Wesleyan University.
    - Summer at the Center. Events for July 4 to July 18, year unknown. Center for the Arts, Wesleyan University.
    - Summer at the Center. Events for July 26 to August 2, year unknown. Center for the Arts, Wesleyan University.
    - Summer at the Center. Events for July 19 to July 26, year unknown. Center for the Arts, Wesleyan University, 2 copies
    - Women and Wesleyan. Wesleyan University is now accepting applications from women students for admission to the freshman class which will enter the University in the fall of 1970...
    - Picture of Wesleyan Professors, Wesleyan University. Middletown, Connecticut, undated.
    - Announcing the 1969-1970 Percival Wood Clement Competition, for best essay submitted, undated.
    - Ceremony Guide: Sesquicentennial Convocation 1831-1981. Wesleyan University. Sunday Sept. 20, 1981.
    - He had a Dream and the Dream Still Lives. A Community Celebration for Martin Luther King's Birthday. January 16, 1977. The First Church of Christ Congregational, 190 Court Street. Middletown, CT.
    - Inauguration Concert. Memorial Chapel. October 20, 1967. Performers: Jon Brlow, Raymond Rendall, pianists; Richard Winslow, conductor; The Wesleyan Chamber Orchestra, Isaac Hurwitz, Conductor.
    - University Convocation. An Address by President Colin G. Campbell. Crowell Concert Hall. September 9, year unknown.
    - Wesleyan Baseball, schedule, 1970.
    - Abraham Bloemaert, The Adoration of the Shepherds. Davison Art Center, 1966.
    - William Shakespeare. Documentary by S. Schoenbaum Printed by Oxford University Press, 1975.
    - Studio Party, Davison Art Center at the barn, Wesleyan Hills. May 23, 1970.
    - A Great Week for Writers at Wesleyan University. Wesleyan Writers Conference. July 20-27.
    - Careers in Energy and Environment. Sponsored by Wesleyan Alumni Association. Fisk Hall. March 30, 1979.
    - Careers in Communications. Sponsored by Wesleyan Alumni Association. Fisk Hall. April 2, 1982
    - 1976 Connecticut College Summer Session. New London, Connecticut, 1976.
    - Photo reproduction: Plate Six: The Hogarth Engraving. Davison Art Center
    - Photo reproduction: Plate Three: The Hogarth Engraving. Davison Art Center
    - Jasper Johns, Prints 1970-1977. Center for the Arts. March 27-April 25,1978. (Folder 7)
    - Jacqueline Gourevitch, Cloud Paintings 1964-1971. Oct. 8-24, Davison Art Center.
    - Philip Pearlstein. Prints, Drawings, Paintings. Center for the Arts. September 7-October 7, 1979.
    - Positive Images. Portraits by Barbara Woike. North Gallery, Center for the Arts. May 7-13, 1979.
    - Sculptors and Their Drawings. Selections from the Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden. North Gallery, Center for the Arts. January 24-February 29, 1976, 2 copies.
    - The American Space. Nineteenth Century landscape portraits from the Collection of Daniel Wolf. Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery, Center for the Arts. May 8-July 21, 1984.
    - Society of Connecticut Craftsmen Annual Exhibition, Gallery, Center for the Arts. June 21-July 27, 1975.
    - Alex Katz. Davison Art Center. March 9-April 21,1974, 2 copies
    - Jeff Silverthorne Photographs. Main Gallery, Center for the Arts. February22-March 10, 1977.
    - Images of Death, Davison Art Center. January 25-March 2, 1975.
    - One Times Four Times Four, John Schiebold. South Gallery, Center For the Arts. January. 19-February13, no year.
    - Woodworks, Davison Art Center. May 3-June 5.
    - Rembrandt and his Followers, Yale University Art Gallery, February 13-April 6. Davison Art Center, May 2-June 8, 1980.
    - The Transforming Eye. Photographs by Clarence John Laughlin. Davison Art Center. January 11-February 11, 1977.
    - Satish Gujral. Works in Three Dimensions. November 15-December 20, 1974. North Gallery, Center for the Arts.
    - Oskar Kokoschka. Literary and Graphic Works, 1906-1923. Center for the Arts Gallery. November 1-December 21, 1975.
    - Dirty Sheets: Graphic Art for Highly Graphic Motion Pictures. South Gallery, Center for the Arts. Sept. 6-Oct. 16, year unknown.
    - The First Traveling Offset Rip-Off Show. South Gallery, Center for the Arts. Dec. 6-20, 1974.
    - Poster Exhibit. Posters of Wesleyan Events by William Van Saun. January 10-February 4. Davison Art Center.
    - Franklin R. Drake. Davison Art Center. March 12-April 4, 1971.
    - Kunst Als Kultur/Art as Culture. Recent art from: George Baselitz, Lothar Baumgarten, Rebecca Horn, Jorg Immendorff, Anselm Kiefer, A.R. Penck, Sigmar Polke, Arnulf Rainer, Gerhard Richter. August 27-October 19, 1986. Ezra and Cecile Zilkha Gallery.
    - An Exhibition of Graphic Design by Anita K. Hersh. May 6-18, 1976. Jones Room, Theater Studios, Center for the Arts.
    - Eric Ryan. Electric Signs. Davison Art Center. March 12-April 4, 1971.
    - The Prints of Amand Seguin (1869-1903). February 8-March 14, 1980. Davison Art Center.
    - Jasper Johns, Prints 1970-1977. Center for the Arts. March 27-April 25, 1978, 2 copies.
    - Painting Now. Paintings from the Aldrich Museum. January.19-February 13, 1977. Main Gallery, Center for the Arts.
    - Dreams for Sale. The Great Work of Hollywood Still Photographers (1927-1949). Center for the Arts Gallery. Sept. 2- Oct. 16, 1977.
    - American Photographs from the collection of Russell G. D'Oench. Davison Art Center. Nov. 3-26, 1978.
    - J. Seeley. Recent Work. February 19- March 11, 1977. Davison Art Center.
    - Jacqueline Gourevitch. Recent Paintings and Drawings. Sept. 2- Oct. 2, 1977. Center for the Arts, South Gallery. Sept. 2, year unknown.
    - Andre Kertesz. Photographs. January 23-February 20, 1976. Davison Art Center.
    - Harry Nadler. Paintings/Drawings. Davison Art Center. February 12-March. 7, 1971.
- Posters, 1968-1998
  - CFA/Zilkha Gallery Posters (Drawer 3, Folder 1)
    - Views of Rome. Giovanni Battista Piranesi. CFA Gallery. September 8-October 13, 1978
    - G.W. Smith. Recent Work. CFA South Gallery. February 16 - March 10.
    - Idea Art. CFA South Gallery. Nov 10 - Dec 15, 1977.
    - Jacqueline Gourevitch. Recent Paintings and Drawings. CFA South Gallery. September 2-October 2, 1977.
    - Painting Now. Paintings from the Aldrich Museum. CFA Main Gallery. January 19 - February 13 1977.
    - American Art in the Making. Preparatory Studies for Masterpieces of American Painting 1800-1900. CFA Gallery. July 3 - Aug 1 1976.
    - Satish Gujral. Works in Three Dimensions. CFA North Gallery. Nov 15 - Dec 20 1974.
    - Dirty Sheets. A Restricted sampling of John Raymond Foster's vast private collection of advertising posters for feature films. Sept. 6 - Oct 16 1975.
    - Arabesques: Mary Kring Risley & David Schorr. CFA Gallery. Sep 13 - Oct 16, 1975.
    - Jacqueline Gourevitch. An Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings. January 27 - Mar 25, 1983.
    - Dana Asbury. Photographs. CFA North Gallery. September 10-28.
    - Michael Januarytzen. Exploratory Observations. CFA Main Gallery. Nov 1 - Dec 15, 1977.
    - New Architecture in New England. CFA Gallery. November 2-28 1977. On verso: New Ideas in Clay. CFA North Gallery. Oct 30 - Dec 5, 1977.
    - Danny Dries. Rhythm Step Matrix. CFA South Gallery. Oct 5, 1977
    - Alphabets. Joseph Reed. Paintings and Etchings since 1965. CFA Gallery. January 26 - Mar 10, 1978.
    - Kathakali - Dance Theater from India. CFA, Nov 15, 1973.
    - The American Space: Nineteenth Century Landscape Photographs from the Collection of Daniel Wolf. Zilkha Gallery. May 8-July 21, 1984.
  - Davison Art Center Events, 1970-1987 (Folder 2)
    - William Van Saun: Posters of Wesleyan Events. Davison Art Center. January 10- February 4, year unknown
    - American Photographs from the Collection of Russell G. D'Oench. Davison Art Center. Nov 3 -26, 1978.
    - Portraits In Prints. Davison Art Center. February 24 - Mar 10, 1978.
    - American Prints 1889-1945. Davison Art Center. Mar 10 - Apr 11, 1976.
    - Recent American Etching. Davison Art Center. Oct 10 - Nov 23, 1974. (2 copies)
    - Eric Ryan: Electric Signs. Davison Art Center. Mar 12- Apr 4, 1971.
    - Modern Master Tapestries. Davison Art Center. Oct 23- Nov 25, 1970.
    - Franklin R. Drake. Davison Art Center. Mar 12 - Apr 4, 1971. (2 copies)